# DAVID EISENMENGER

#### USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

www.eisenmenger.co david@eisenmenger.co

## **ABOUT ME**

A user experience designer with a background in program development.

My mission is to add value to others. A more than ten year career in the healthcare industry working with people who are part of vulnerable populations led me to develop a passion for improving services that benefit the lives of other people. I bring this passion to my work with digital products and services.

# **SKILLS**

User Research

**Experience Design** 

Wireframing

Prototyping

**Usability Testing** 

**Design Strategy** 

Systems Thinking

## TOOLS

Figma & Sketch

**InVision** 

Adobe Photoshop

Illustrator & InDesign

WordPress

Webflow

HTML & CSS

### **EXPERIENCE**

Ardea Design LLC

Oct 2019 - Present

Freelance Designer

User experience design and consulting

Trenaman Law, Legal Firm

Strategized and developed UX and UI solutions for a new landing page Updated branding to reflect client's values and tenure

Tech for Campaigns, Political Campaign

Designed new websites as part of a cross-functional team

Delivered UI design for a variety of campaign tools

MedWater, Nonprofit Organization

Initiated strategic review of user processes

Developed a prototype to streamline the organization's donation process

Friendship Health Director of Social Services Feb 2016 - April 2019

Developed strategy for customer service for aging care population

Signature Healthcare, LLC Director of Education and Research

Oct 2009 - Feb 2016

Researched and developed training programs for Inc 5000 healthcare organization Delivered programs on Palliative Care, Diversity & Inclusion to 113 facilities

## **CERTIFICATES**

**User Experience Design** 

Springboard
Credential ID 22090

Front End Web Development

Code Louisville May 2018

### **EDUCATION**

**BA Peace and Global Studies** 

Earlham College

MA Marriage and Family Therapy

Louisville Presbyterian Theological Seminary